

RAKHEOANA LEFELA

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

PERSONAL INFORMATION

Passport No: RC858180 (work permit)

Lives: Cape Town Willing to relocate: Yes

Overall web development experience: 4 year

Email: rakgew@gmail.com

Address: 20 Roseville Road, Claremont LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/rakheoana-

lefela-21a36051/ Cell: +27 78 375 4146

SKILLS

Coding Languages

C#, ASP.NET JavaScript, HTML/CSS, PHP, MySQL. Typescript.

Frameworks/Systems

MVC, Laravel, React, bootstrap, Visual Studio, VScode, Git, Node.js, Microsoft SQL Server Management studio, XAMP, Azure DevOps Docker

EDUCATIONAL TRAINING

Limkokwing University (Lesotho)

Bachelor of Science: Information Technology (e-commerce)

• Enrolled from Sept. 2008 to Dec 2012

PROFILE

I am a web developer with 4+ years of experience and an Honors degree in information technology. I am experienced in all the stages of the project development lifecycle of dynamic web projects using JavaScript, CSS, MySQL, C#.NET, PHP and html.

SOFT SKILLS

Coding Languages

Teamwork.
Communication.
Yes attitude.
Service-focused.
Strong decision making .

HOW I SHARPEN MY SKILLS

Codility

I love doing algorithm challenges on codility and project UELA, even though this is just a recently found hobby, it has become one of my favorite things to do.

Udemy

From time to time I take a Udemy course to learn a new skill or to gain in-depth knowledge of a language I already know.

Projects

I like taking on private projetcs that I may use practically to speed up my productivity or that I can share with others to use.

CAREER SUMMARY

DESIGN GURU

Role

Intern PHP developer | Sept 2015 - Dec 2015 Responsibilities

- Make static websites dynamic using PHP and MySQL backend.
- · Modifies code to fix errors
- Build email templates.

Tools used

Apache | jQuery & JavaScript | bootstrap | PHP CSS | HTML5

LUCIDOCEAN

Role

software developer | Jul 2018 - Mar 2021 Responsibilities

- Build new features for existing projects.
- Upgrading ASP.net projects UI to modern bootstrap versions.
- Administered large Data collection web applications and their database.
- Building PWA applications.

Tools used

Apache | jQuery, JavaScript & Typescript | bootstrap | PHP | CSS | Seahorse | MVC Cordova , Ionic | iignition.js | node. Grunt, Gulp

WEMASOFT

Role:

software developer | Jun 2021 - Nov 2021 Responsibilities

- Build new features for existing projects.
- Project development life-cycle
- Team lead
- · Allocating tasks
- Evaluating team performance
- Selecting Technology to upgrade existing systems
- Liaising with CTO.

Tools used

Apache | jQuery, JavaScript | bootstrap | PHP | CSS | Zend Framework | Html 5 | cPanel

WHAT I AM LOOKING FOR IN MY NEXT JOB

Roles

Web developer software Engineer web stack developer PHP developer

Tech

PHP (Laravel / zend). Python. C# ASP.Net with Razor & JS, Blazor .Net / .Net core Web API with Management studio React / vue js

REFERENCES

DESIGN GURU

Web Developer, [PHP developer @ design guru 2015] Gevann Mullins

Cell: +27789298581

Email: gevann.mullins@gmail.com

LUCIDOCEAN (NOW SOLITAN LONDON)

CE0

Jonathan Crossland

Email: Jonathancrossland@gmail.com

Wemasoft

CEO, MD

David Kintonga

Cell: +27711708473 Email:info@wemasoft.co.za



@LefelaR



https://www.linkedin.com/in/rakheoana-lefela-21a36051/



@lefelaR



https://codepen.io/lefelar/



http://3.136.224.69/